What can we do now?
I will only have few gates in Distyr.
Asuna.
Siyune!
Please, do you know what happened to Yuki?
It's been three days and
she hasn't logged back in.
It's not just you.
None of us have been able
to contact her either.
Asuna, I hate to say this, but I don't
think she wants to see you again.
I think she's doing it for your own good.
But why?
I had a feeling something wasn't right.
I could tell everyone in the group
was avoiding getting too close to me.
The last thing I want is to
upset anyone, or be a nuisance.
But still, I don't see how any
of this could be for my sake!
You're not a nuisance!
It's not like that.
Believe me when I say we're all
truly happy to have met you.
We got to have one last amazing
memory of our time together here.
And it's all thanks to you.
And Yuki, I know she's grateful too.
But please, forget you ever met us.
It really is the best
thing for you and for Yuki.
I can't ever see any of you again.
I thought after the guild was gone,
I thought we could at least
keep on being friends.
But this whole time, I was
the only one who thought that?
I'm sorry.
No, wait!
Oh, give it for my way
Asuna!
Morning!
Morning, Asuna! Good morning.
Oh, we finally caught you.
All right, we're here.
So you gotta tell us what
that message was about?
Is it true?
Well, I said something
about you joining a guild.
Come on, come on, tell us.
Are they cool?
Well, it's like...
Oh, hang on a sec.
All right, how's that?
Can you see my face okay?
I see you, but you're a little blurry.
Hmm, it's the autofocus again.
It's got to be that.
Give me a sec, Yui. Okay, Daddy.
Hey.
This second, you still want to see her?
Even after they say it's better
you didn't, you still do?
I don't care what they say.
All I want is to talk
to Yuki one last time.
I can't leave it like this. Okay.
I think I might have found where she's at.
I'm not sure, but it's the best I got.
What makes you think she'd be here?
That place has a medicuboid.
They're the only ones doing
the clinical trials for it.
Medicuboid?
Excuse me. May I help you? Yes.
I, um, I think I'm looking for a patient.
Well, she's about 15 years old or so.
I think her name might be
Yuki, but I'm not sure.
I need a name, at least.
Oh, um, well, I think she might be the
patient who's testing that Medicuboid thing.
Pardon me, miss.
What's your name?
Oh, sorry.
My name is Asuna Yuki.
Please, have a seat.
I'll get someone right away.
Sure.
Hi.
Sorry about that.
I hope you haven't been waiting long.
No, not at all. That's good.
They told me you're Asuna Yuki?
Yes. Great. I'm Dr. Kurohashi.
I'm Yuki Kono's primary physician.
Yuki Kono.
You know, I'm surprised
you even found us. Why?
Oh, well, we keep a
low profile. That said,
Yuki warned me someone called Asuna might
try and pay her a visit at some point.
She warned you?
Uh-huh.
She also said she didn't
tell you where she was.
So I said, don't worry about it.
She's not going to find you here.
When reception told me you were
in the lobby, I was shocked.
Doctor, has Yuki told you anything
else about me or how we met?
I'll say she has.
You're pretty much the only
person she talks about.
Although, it seems whenever Yuki does
mention you, she always ends up in tears.
She's always been a brave girl
and never felt sorry for herself.
She wants to see you, but she
can't bring herself to do it.
Yes, I know, and I still
can't wrap my head around it.
A friend of hers told me in-game
that it was for my own good.
Why is that?
Why can't we see each other?
For starters I should tell you what the
medicuboid is about okay medicuboid is the
code name for the World's first medical
full dive machine it's so revolutionary the
government's backing its Development it's
a full dive rig for hospitals uh-huh for
example let's say you're a patient With a
visual or hearing disability this machine
can give you back those senses you know
how with The atmosphere rig images and
sounds get sent directly
to your brain well
transmitting signals Isn't all it does the
atmosphere has the ability to cancel out
physical sensations too
back here It hits that
spot with electromagnetic pulses so it
temporarily numbs the
nerves it's kind of like
general anesthetic.
Okay, but how is that
useful for hospitals?
There's a limit to how much
the atmosphere can block out.
What happens if a patient's in serious
pain? Exactly.
You hit the nail right on the head.
The atmosphere can't do it.
Even
the nerve gear can't block pain
from surgery or chronic illness.
However, the medicuboid enhances
the electromagnetic pulse.
Plus, it's built into the
bed so there's more coverage.
The brain, spine, everything.
Once it gets on the market, it'll change
the course of medicine as we know it.
The medicuboid has incredible potential.
You could, say, pair it with the
camera and give it an AR function.
The patient gets real-world
images in real time. That's great.
Sounds more like a miracle
than a machine to me.
Yes.
In a way, it is a miracle.
Even so, curing illness
is something it can't do.
The Medicuboid is making
an impact, though.
We hope.
In terminal care.
Terminal care?
Yes.
It's helping patients who are dying.
She's dying?
Yuki told me that if you really wanted
to hear about what's going on with her,
I could go ahead and tell you.
But I have to warn you,
it's not a pleasant story.
You're going to wish this
conversation ended right here.
No.
I want to hear it. The whole thing.
And I'm not leaving
here until you tell me.
Yuki was born in May of 2011.
But there were complications, and the
doctors had to give her mother a C-section.
Her mother was given a
transfusion during the procedure.
But unfortunately, the blood they
used was contaminated with a virus.
They didn't find out
about it until September,
when her mother was having tests
run for an infection she got.
But by that time, the whole
family'd been infected.
This way.
We have to keep the room on the other
side of the glass, hermetically sealed,
so this is as close as you can get.
I hope you understand.
Yuki.
Doctor, what kind of
illness does Yuki have?
Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome.
AIDS for short.
It's caused by the hiv
virus it's scary but
there's hope because
not everyone who has it
develops aids if you can
treat hiv early you can
have a long life in her
family's case the virus
was difficult to treat
it's a drug resistant
strain when her mother
found out she got so upset
over her children's fate
she actually considered
killing the whole family
along with herself
but then she changed her
mind and decided to fight
the disease instead she
fought it for her kids
yes soon after they were diagnosed
yuki was put on a multi-drug
course of therapy but it's hard
for a child to have to take so many
different medications and keep
taking them the side effects are one
thing the other being shunned by
people who don't understand her?
condition.
Still, Yuki was a trooper.
She believed her and her family
would get better eventually.
However, when she was in the fourth grade,
her immune system suddenly collapsed.
And then,
she was brought to this hospital, and
that's when she was diagnosed with AIDS.
But like I said, she's a trooper.
She never once lost her optimism.
him.
Doctor?
Why is she using the medicuboid?
I guess you could say
it all started back when
everyone was panicking over
that nerve gear incident.
They had just completed the first
prototype of the medicuboid.
The electromagnetic pulses it put out were
many times stronger than the nerve gears.
That was a problem, since no one knew what
the long-term effects of exposure were.
Because of that, they couldn't find
a patient willing to take the risk,
so its trial run was stalled.
When I found out, I thought about Yuki's
situation, and I contacted her parents.
If she were the test subject, she'd be
moved to the medicuboid sterile room.
She'd run less of a risk
of getting an infection.
I told them it was a great opportunity.
At least that's what I thought.
But honestly, I still don't know
if I was right to suggest it.
God knows what it was like
for Yuki and her parents.
Thinking about whether or not to accept.
But I think the lure of the unknown.
The virtual world.
Was the deciding factor for Yuki.
So that brave little girl
agreed to be a test subject.
And they moved her in.
She's lived inside the Medicuboid.
Ever since.
You mean she's never come out?
No, she hasn't.
Yuki stays logged in and rarely
spends any time in the real world.
She's always in a lot of pain, but thanks
to the Medicuboid Sensation Canceller,
she can block it out.
So wait, you mean she's
in a continuous Hero dive?
Since when?
For three years now.
That's a whole year longer than us.
It felt like they were a product of
the full-dive environment itself.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'm glad I got to see her again.
She'll be okay as long
as she's here, right?
We're doing everything we can for her.
But even if the room is sterile,
there's no way to eliminate
the virus that's inside her.
What do you mean?
Yuki doesn't have much time left.
And that's most likely the reason why she
tried cutting ties with
you the way she did.
That's why she...
Yuki!
Asuna, I...
We did it!
Leave it to me, sis!
Um, doctor?
I was wondering, does
Yuki have an older sister?
Uh, yes, actually.
A twin sister, to be precise.
Her name's Aiko, and she was
born a few minutes earlier.
Yuki was the cheerful one.
In fact, Aiko would just sit
and watch her, and smile.
Come to think of it, if Aiko were here,
I'd imagine she'd be a lot like you.
Where is she?
Yuki's parents passed away two years ago.
And last year, Aiko.
Yuki...
Don't cry, Asuna!
Yuki! Yuki!
You can hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
I can see you, too.
Wow.
You look exactly like you do in the game.
Thanks for coming to see me.
Yuki...
I just... I don't...
Hey, Doc.
Would it be okay if Asuna
used the room next door?
Sure, why not?
I keep an atmosphere in
there so I can visit her.
Go ahead, it's all yours.
Thanks.
The ALO app's on the startup menu.
After you log in, come to the
place where we first met, okay?
I want to see you.
I want to see you one more time.
And this time I want to
talk to you for real.
Huh?
Yuki!
I knew it.
I don't know how you did it, but I had a
feeling you'd find me in the real world,
somehow.
And I was so careful not to say
nothing, thought I had you fooled.
It didn't work, you found me anyway.
I must be turned and psychic, cause
my predictions never come true.
But I'm happy, really.
My sis used to hug me like this.
You smell like her.
Like the sun.
Did I go play Fairy
Memos with you two? Yep.
In fact, she was the first leader
the Sleeping Knights ever had.
And if you thought I was strong,
man, you should have seen her.
We met Siyunay and the other guys in this
virtual hospice called the Serene Garden.
Back then, there were nine of us.
But my sis and Clovis and Merida...
Well, they're all gone.
Anyway, if you want to
know why we're disbanding?
It's cause we promised each other
if we lost someone, we'd end it!
I'm sorry, Asuna.
That's why I couldn't tell you.
The sleeping knights won't be
around anymore by this spring.
But it's not cause we'll all
be too busy to play anymore.
It's cause a little while ago, two
of us got the news from our doctors.
They gave us three months.
You see that's why we were all so
fired up on having one last big
adventure together in this world we
wanted to leave some kind of proof we
were here on that big old monument
where everyone can see it one last
run that was so cool we could brag
about it to my sis and the others
but nothing was going right for
us so we decided the best way to
get there was to get someone tough
enough to help but we just caused
you trouble and we hurt your
feelings too i'm sorry we all are
forget about us it's probably for
the best anyway i can't do that
i'm happy i got to meet you all of you and
i'm glad i got to be a
part of your last quest.
Even after everything, I still
wish I could join the Knights.
Yeah, I wish, I wish you could too, but
I'm happy I came here and got to meet you.
You saying that makes it
worth it, more than worth it.
That's enough for me. I'm good.
But isn't there anything
else you want to do? I mean,
I'm sure there's lots of places
in all time you haven't been yet,
And other virtual worlds,
There's still lots of things
to do and places to see,
You can't tell me you've had enough!
For the last three years, We got to go
on tons of adventures in other worlds,
But I want my very last memory To be
the one I got to go on with you, Asuna.
Yeah, but can't you think of anything
else you want to see? Or maybe do?
I don't know.
I guess maybe go to school again
for real no forget it just kidding!
I'm happy you want to help but don't sweat
it it's cool I had an awesome life really!
Maybe you can wait what maybe
you can go you know to school?
I love you, I love you.
Do you know how much I can tell you?
I always feel like I can tell you.
I don't know if you don't know.
I'm sure you don't know.
I don't know if I can tell you!
I can tell you. I am
Next time, the dream begins.